You are
weak right now.
So,
you want to kill me while you can.
As long as I kill you,
my brothers and I will be free.
Just based on that,
you want to kill me?
Better than you, Capital Director.
Schemed against by a despicable villain.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
You are still provoking me at this time.
What a nerve you have.
I have no need to be afraid of you.
Let me ask you,
normally,
have I
held a deep grudge against you?
Let me ask you again,
have I ever mistreated you?
I killed and burned before,
just so my dog brothers and I could survive.
But since entering the Ice Well Agency,
though we lost our freedom,
at least they have a home.
If you kill me,
you will,
just like in the past,
be like stray dogs,
wandering around.
If you act as bandits again,
who will protect your lives?
Furthermore,
though I'm temporarily in trouble,
my Chu family
has received the Emperor's grace
and holds a gold medal granted by him.
As long as I hold the gold medal,
I can enter the palace to see him.
How can those filthy villains
bring me down
just by saying so?
Brother Chaijiu, you are here.
Lord Chu.
Now that Brother Chaijiu has left the Ice Well Agency,
you're not still thinking of controlling him, are you?
Brother Chaijiu,
I'm in a hurry to go back to find my sister-in-law and sister.
Are you coming with me
or staying here?
Your sister-in-law and sister are not at home.
But they are in a safe place.
You captured his family?
Capital Director.
He will definitely come back to find me.
If you feel bad,
just wait for him here.
Sister-in-law, Sister.
The stove is cold.
Xiaolian is weak and can't leave the house.
Could they really have been taken by Chu Sanniang?
Usually, if I knock with the secret code,
someone will answer the door.
It seems Mr. Zhou knows I'm a wanted man,
so he's avoiding me.
I must catch the assassin myself
to prove my innocence.
Sir.
I know where the thief is.
Is it her?
Yes.
Daughter.
How dare you!
How could I possibly
help you solve a case?
If this is successful,
I will naturally help you find
your long-lost daughter.
Search carefully!
Keep your eyes peeled.
Officers,
it's just ahead.
You few,
go over there.
Look carefully!
Nothing here.
Nothing here either.
Nothing found.
Bastard!
How dare you mess with me!
They were just there.
Look, the fire isn't even out yet.
If you make another false report,
I'll take your miserable life!
Withdraw!
Yes, sir.
How dare you report to the authorities!
You dared to take my sister-in-law and sister!
Brother Meng,
calm down.
Calm down.
She took my sister-in-law and sister.
I can't calm down!
Calm down.
Where are my sister-in-law and sister?
Where on earth are they?
If you want to know,
then do something for me.
Do what?
I will personally catch those
Liangshan assassins who entered Wuyou City with you.
You
lead
the way.
Brother Chaijiu.
This is Luoshifang.
Luoshifang again.
They just left.
Look.